Thanks Raido, with that in mind let's add
a Refresh Menu button to our app. For temporary
purposes only though, otherwise Raido would be mad at
us. On Android, menu options are defined in XML
and they can be declared for fragments or
activities. When the fragment or activity is created, it
inflates this XML into the actual menu items in
the app. You'll see that there are Action buttons
which are menu items that appear in the Action bar,
such as this Search Menu item. This space is reserved
for the most prominent actions in your app. Then anything
else that's less important falls into the overflow menu by
tapping on this button with the three dots. These menu
items are ordered from most frequently used to least frequently
used. And on larger devices that have more screen real
estate, you can specify that some of these menu items can
actually go into the Action bar if there's room. If
you go back to our project in the Resources folder
which is called res, there is a Menu folder and
inside that there's a main.xml file. If you open that up
you see the menu layout XML, and that there's a
single menu option defined for Settings. It will never show up
as an action in the Action bar, meaning that it
will be in the Overflow menu. You can verify this by
checking the app on your phone. To define the ordering
of menu items, you can just add multiple items to this
XML file, and then they will show up in that order
in the app. If you don't like the order though, and
you want to explicitly set it, then you can specify
this order in Category, value. Right now it's set as 100,
so that the Settings menu will be at the bottom of
all the other menu options that we define in our app.
The only Menu option that should show up below the Settings
menu is the Help menu. Check out the link for more details.